[CHAPTER.3]
[Take the first step, and the heavens will follow]
[Egypt Trip DAY 2]
[EGYPT DAY 2]
[Good morning!]
[Is it really a good morning...?]
[Same morning, different fate]
[In the desert morning,]
[one lone tent flaps in the wind]
[The sound of coughing
wakes the desert]
Ugh, it's so cold.
[Only a sleeping bag to keep warm...]
Oh, my back is killing me…
[The 44-year-old leader
whose back hurts from sleeping on the floor]
Ugh…
Agh…
[One by one, they wake up]
How long did we even sleep?
[Our pauper leader's feeling homesick]
I want to go home.
[His complaints intensified overnight]
Take me home.
Ugh, my back hurts.
At least we're still alive…
[Thankfully, the paupers
made it through the night]
Are we seriously stranded here?
The moment we opened
our eyes in the morning,
the sandy winds woke us up.
The sand was our blankets.
[Pauper-exclusive sand blankets & sand alarm clock]
And the sandy wind was our alarm clock.
[Meanwhile, morning also arrives
at the princes' accommodation]
[Here's your breakfast, Your Highness]
Come in.
Oh!
[Breakfast room service to enjoy in comfort]
Welcome!
Would you like it outside?
[The terrace is perfect]
It'd be great out there. Okay!
I swung open the terrace door
and stepped out…
Gasp!
[The pyramid view that took the prince's breath away]
The pyramid was right in front of my eyes!
It was literally just there.
It was so beautiful.
It was a spectacular sight.
[DAWN settles in the best spot]
[Sipping on morning coffee]
This is so nice.
[Taking in the pyramid view]
Oh, but the view is insane.
It feels like
[Feeling like ancient Egyptian royalty]
I'm Pharaoh's 6th cousin or something.
[As he reveals his ambition to be a prince twice in a row]
I'm gonna be a prince today too.
I promised myself all night long
as I was sleeping.
Wow, bread.
[YOHAN happily devours his breakfast]
[Egyptian bread never lets you down]
Mhm! Mhm!! Mhm!!!
[Crunchy]
[So happy with just a piece of bread]
This is really good.
I'm actually
not a fan of those things.
[Not a fan of American breakfast?]
I don't really like American breakfast.
(The toast mukbang
of someone who doesn't like it)
Mhm!
Why is it toasted perfectly?
Mmm!
[How much does he eat when he likes something then?]
Mhm!
[After getting full, he gets curious about the paupers]
They must get breakfast, right?
[Technically, yes]
Agh…
[One piece of bread]
[And multivitamins]
Vitamins.
This is kind of...
[Utter disbelief]
Look at this.
You can't be a pauper again, huh?
I'm totally gonna be a prince today.
[The paupers eat their breakfast]
[The mealtime is
filled with heavy silence]
[Even Romantic JOHNNY]
It's my first time eating
[struggles to eat plain bread in the morning]
bread that doesn't taste like anything.
Is there a sauce
or anything to dip this in?
[Miserable from the morning]
Ugh!!!
It really doesn't
taste like anything.
[Meanwhile, the sandy wind shakes up their house]
I think we're gonna fly away, LEETEUK.
Just looking at the condition
of our shoes from yesterday…
[In just one day,]
Hey, are we just paupers?
[he got downgraded from NCT to pauper]
It's not that we look like paupers, we are paupers!
How long do we have
to stay as paupers?
[After tidying up and returning]
After you tidy up and return,
[Their status will be reset!]
your status will reset.
Let's hurry up!
[Let's escape this pauper life ASAP!]
(Quickly moving
to boost our status)
[Escaping the dreadful tent]
Let's go!
[Next, JOHNNY]
[and JISUNG escapes too!]
Oh, JISUNG…
[The prince fit they've been wearing since yesterday]
We were wearing the prince suits, right?
So the suit was white at first,
[Transformed into a Desert Sand edition]
but it's beige now.
I just looked so pathetic.
For me, being a pauper is…
[Something he never wants to do again]
an experience where once is enough.
Let's go.
[There will be no more pauper life]
Ugh, I'm feeling dizzy.
[The first social status reset]
Day 1 social status
resets in "ALL or NOTHING"!]
[To get started
on their new itinerary]
Alright, paupers, come on in!
[WANGGEOZ are all gathered together again]
Oh, princes, you look great.
Paupers, come on in.
[They look worlds apart]
But your faces look refreshed.
How was it, Team Pauper?
[Most interested in the pauper accommodation]
Seriously, how was it? Tell us exactly.
Since we have no idea.
I'll be honest.
Look to the right side.
[That's it right there]
It's that. Yeah, it's that.
[Not the building in front]
You slept in a place that nice?
[The mountains in the back]
You see that mountain at the end, right?
- You see that mountain at the end, right?
- Oh, that mountain?
Come on, don't lie.
Come on,
it wouldn't be to that extent!
It really doesn't seem like it, right?
[It's so real that it's just funny...]
Just watch the broadcast.
We slept in
a place like that, on the left.
(Still doubtful)
No way, I don't believe you. I'll watch the show later.
Did you all share a room?
[One tent!]
Yeah, just one tent.
[A tent????]
Oh, it was a tent?
Come on, don't lie.
Come on!
[The princes just can't imagine it]
Who even uses tents these days?
Yeah, why would
you use tents here?
It's even funnier
that they don't believe us.
[The communication struggle between classes]
This is why I'm being honest,
because I didn't think
they'd believe me.
You had a bed, right?
We did not.
[Your Highness… What tent has a bed?]
Come on!
It wasn't a bed,
but what was it called?
[No beds, just sleeping bags]
A sleeping bag.
Sleeping bags are nice!
[Eyes shut tightly]
- Sleeping bags are so warm.
- That must've been so romantic.
[The silent pauper leader begins to stir]
But you can feel the rocks underneath. The gravel.
Oh, come on.
It's like a barren wasteland...
No one would know
if a wolf came and snatched you away at night.
I'd believe you
if you were bitten.
I'd believe you if you were
bitten by a wolf, but you weren't.
[Believe it or not]
You only drove on paved roads, huh?
You only went
on smooth roads, huh?
[Only the paupers find this funny]
Why?
We thought
our car was getting blasted.
[Last night's exciting
off-road adventure]
How much of
what we said do you believe?
[Not a single word]
I believe none of it.
Really?
It's nonsense.
[Instead of a blanket, the sand covered them]
You know, blankets? Do you know what it was?
- What was the blanket?
- The blanket was sand.
We were talking yesterday,
and it felt like
sand was getting stuck in my teeth.
You must've gotten
your teeth properly cleaned then.
Definitely.
It's kind of like this.
(Subtly recommending it)
It's one of those experiences
you should try
at least once in life.
[Then you keep doing it]
You can keep experiencing it, then.
Everyone, do you know this?
The feeling of waking up,
opening your eyes,
and seeing
a pyramid in front of you?
- A pyramid?
- A pyramid was in front of you?
Seriously!
[This time, a world the paupers can't even imagine]
That was the view when we woke up.
- Amazing, right?
- It was a total pyramid view.
[Just envious...]
And this is the terrace.
You just open up
the terrace door…!
Oh, it was really amazing!
The hotel was fantastic.
[The paupers didn't even have time for photos…]
We had a mental breakdown yesterday,
so we didn't even think
to take pictures.
Taking photos
didn't even cross our minds.
After being a prince once…
Was it so great?
Wow…
- I don't think I can go down from there.
- Yeah, I don't think I can.
Yeah, DAWN,
your face looks better than yesterday.
[Looking posh]
Yes.
What worries me is that
I feel like
I'll never become a prince.
I think LEETEUK still
doesn't understand yesterday's game.
[Still figuring out yesterday's game]
Still?
Do it one more time.
[About to take a break]
Take a break, everyone.
- Oh, I'm so tired.
- I think we're almost there.
[But they're already there?]
We're already there?
[It's an empty desert, where exactly is "almost there"?]
What do you mean we're there? There's nothing!
No, this is the entrance
to the airport.
Oh, really?
SHINDONG,
this is where we slept.
If someone told you
to sleep here, could you?
[The clash between the princes and paupers continues]
They really don't believe us! It's getting annoying now.
That's ridiculous.
Why would you sleep there?
[Our second stop of the trip]
[Arrived at the actual destination!]
We're almost at the airport.
Let's go to our next stop!
[The next stop is Luxor]
We'll see you at the next stop, Luxor!
Luxor?
What's Luxor?
[Heading to the second location
on a domestic flight]
[On the east of the Nile River,
where the sun rises]
[A land full of
brilliant ancient sites]
[The land of the living]
[The world’s greatest open-air museum]
[And on the west of the Nile River,
where the sun sets]
[The tombs of pharaohs]
[and the temples
for royal burials stand tall]
[The land of the dead]
[A city where life and death coexist
on the east and west of the Nile]
[LUXOR]
[Arrived in Luxor, the second stop of the Egypt trip!]
Today's destination is Luxor.
But it feels a bit quieter here.
[Luxor's first impression is already perfect]
I think I like it more here.
[A broader Nile River view than in Cairo]
The Nile River looks bigger here
compared to
what we saw in Cairo.
- It seems wider here.
- Yeah.
And, like,
[So many horses on the street]
there are so many horses here.
There really are so many horses.
My guess is
[A horseback riding mission?]
we might end up riding horses
I saw that thing at the Red Sea.
Riding horses along the Red Sea…
[Saw in an Egypt-related video]
Where they run in the sea.
An extreme sport.
On horseback.
[An activity they're hearing about for the first time]
In the water?
- In the water?
- In the water, in the water.
- Really?
- Yes.
[Let's have DAWN do that for sure]
I hope DAWN really rides a horse.
[The second guess is an ancient site]
Is it an ancient site?
[I like ancient sites]
Ancient sites sound fun.
A treasure hunt
at an ancient site.
[Busy predicting the ancient site mission]
Maybe it's deciphering ancient languages?
Oh, we're already
at the ancient site!
[The ancient sites come into
full view outside the window]
Oh!
[Truly feeling like a proper trip now]
It's really amazing!
So, that's really huge.
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
[The greatest open-air museum]
Wow! Look! Wow!
It's a temple…
Why are there so many people?
Wow!
Because it's a tourist spot.
Wow, wow!
[Totally captivated just looking out the window]
This place is really famous for its temples.
Wow! How is this
still standing after all this time?
This is so fascinating.
There were
so many horses on the street.
And what was really impressive…
Do I call it a temple?
[History woven into everyday life]
Wow, it looked magnificent as it came into view.
[Luxor is right up my alley]
"This place seems more my style."
That thought crossed my mind.
- So our team from yesterday is done now, right?
- Yes.
But I hope
Team Pauper from yesterday
gets to sleep somewhere nice...
[Ex-Team Pauper is touched]
He's so sweet!
He's really sweet.
…in a better pauper accommodation.
Then, if that's the case…
A comfortable
pauper accommodation?
[Hoping for a pauper room upgrade]
Yes, a comfier pauper accommodation.
Oh, yeah, that's nice.
[But the scenery starts to clear out]
There are many buildings, but not many people.
I feel like we're almost there.
There's nothing here, though.
What is this?
Oh, they're pulling the handbrake.
[Murmuring]
What's happening?
They said we'd like it.
[Just then,
the car leaves the road?!]
[They enter a suspicious dirt road]
Oh, we're going off-road.
We're almost at our destination.
[The dirt path continues]
[Anxiety creeps in]
I'm getting nervous again.
But it suddenly feels like
we've entered the Amazon.
This isn't gonna be
like surviving in the wilderness, right?
[What exactly is today's mission…?]
Banana harvesting.
It really felt…
like they were
taking us into the wild…
[Is today's mission an extreme jungle adventure?!]
Is it like surviving on a deserted island?
I thought
it was something like that.
Like starting a fire from scratch.
Oh? But all of a sudden…
Are we getting on a boat?!
What is it?
[After passing
through a spooky banana field]
Oh, what?
Oh? We're getting on a boat!
But I'm scared of boats.
[Where exactly…]
[are we going…?]
[Arrived at a mysterious spot]
[Staff] One of the most
popular experiences in Egypt
[The Nile River cruise tour]
is the Nile River cruise.
Oh!
[Everywhere you set foot
is an ancient site]
[And the heart of Luxor,
the Nile River]
[In a moving 5-star hotel]
[Travel through
Luxor, the city of gods!]
A cruiseee!!
We reserved
[A 2-night, 3-day private cruise trip prepared]
2 nights and 3 days of luxury on a private cruise…
- What?
- No way.
…for all of you.
Does the cruise set sail?
It doesn't, right?
[Of course, it sets sail]
It does.
Really?
I've never slept on a ship before.
A cruise is insane!
What more needs to be said?
[Getting off with high expectations]
Let's go.
Wow, there are even rooms there!
Oh!
There's a pool!
[There's a pool on this ship?!]
Wow!
This place is amazing.
Oh, what is this?
[Excitement explodes the moment they see it]
Isn’t this too good to be true?
You should've told us
to bring swimsuits!
[The grand cruise
awaits the WANGGEOZ]
Isn't this too nice?
Wow!
Like, this is amazing!
- Oh?
- Oh, wait, I'm nervous.
Wow!
[Eyes wide open]
No, like…
Wow!
- This place is so luxurious!
- I know, right?
Wow!
[Revealing the ultimate luxury cruise]
Incredible!
[Past the pool is…]
[The lounge]
[A cozy space
for the ultimate chill]
[Beyond the private bar]
[a dining room]
What is this place?
It's too fancy!
[Mesmerized by the luxury]
Wow, it's so luxurious.
- It smells amazing.
- Yeah, it smells so good.
Open up that room.
Wow, this is it! Wow!
- It's the suite, right?
- Yeah.
Oh, wow!
Wow, the game's over.
- There's a TV.
- Wow, what is this place?
[The main room
of the luxury cruise!]
[A bed with a river view]
[& a dining table]
[Then step inside to find]
[a comfy sofa
and a bathtub for relaxation]
[A suite full of elegance]
[And more premium rooms
with a similar layout!]
Isn't this room
too good to be true?
This room is
definitely the best one.
[The more they explore, the more they want a cruise stay]
Yeah, this place…This place is…
This is the best room.
Let's quickly get to the games
and just sleep.
Sounds good.
[Our cruise that left everyone mesmerized]
Let's sleep luxuriously tonight.
Oh, what now?
[Detecting something suspicious]
This setup feels weird.
Oh, hold on.
[Spotted the suitcases]
The luggage is here! The luggage is here!
[But the suitcases…]
What is this?
[are tied up?]
They're tied up! Wait.
We have to crack the code?
[Their suitcases are chained up]
[You must unlock
the chains to take them]
Oh, come on.
(Assessing the situation)
Oh, so the mission is to get the codes…
Aha!
[It's a game with their suitcases on the line…]
This is going too far!
[An even pettier start than expected]
Way too far!
Oh, what is this?
(It's not gonna be easy today either…)
If this is a 3-digit code…
Hold on a second.
This is legendary...
There's a table here.
[Looks suspicious to anyone]
It's an individual match.
(Going solo today?)
So, the 1st place winner goes in
[The winner gets first pick of the cruise cabins?]
and picks the room they want to use.
- They go in first?
- Yeah.
Oh, it must be that.
Is it?
[This is making us dizzy]
What is it? Tell us!
[Staff] As you've seen on the way,
Your luggage
[Locked with a 3-digit code]
is currently secured with a 3-digit lock.
It's locked.
You must unlock
[After unlocking the code,]
the 3-digit code,
[the first 3 people]
but only the first 3 people
[can hop on the cruise]
can board the luxury cruise.
[A 4-event sports competition to become the princes of "The Solar Barque"]
[Today's main mission]
[The Solar Barque]
[A sports competition with 4 events]
[Reflexes / Dynamic vision]
[Memory / Body fat burning]
[The 4 events will be repeated]
[Those who succeed or win]
[will acquire
one lock code at a time]
[When there are 3 princes,
the game ends!]
This is seriously legendary.
[Heh...]
This is crazy.
[6 suitcases]
Are the numbers different for each suitcase?
[Staff] Yes, they're all different.
[If you know 2 digits,]
But you just need to know 2 digits.
[you can just guess the last digit]
Right, you can just narrow it down.
[Anticipating that,]
Right, we thought you'd do that,
[the suitcase numbers]
so the 3 numbers of the lock
[will be given at random]
will be given to you randomly!
Agh!
[Their sneaky plan fails]
You're too much.
Ha…
But…
It's more annoying
that they predicted this.
[Expecting a rough path ahead]
They're so smart, so smart.
Then what about
the remaining 3 people?
The other 3 people
They'll probably sleep here.
[Legendary (negative)]
Wow, this is truly legendary.
[Not here]
We've rented an entire hotel for the staff.
We'll lend you the rooftop.
[The place where today's paupers will sleep]
[The rooftop of the staff hotel!]
The ship has many rooms…
[Staff] We'll be filming,
so the staff needs to be on board, too.
Sorry about that.
Oh…
Then are we
doing this again tomorrow?
[Pleading for sympathy]
I haven't…
properly unpacked yet.
[Because there was no reason to unpack...]
Ugh…
Ugh…save me…
[Thought we could sleep
comfortably tonight…]
- Oh, yeah.
- Seriously.
- That's true.
I can't remember
what's in my suitcase.
[Troubled]
I can't remember.
It's not gonna be easy
this time either.
But that cruise suite room
is mine.
The cruise was
incredibly luxurious.
It was spotless.
[My bed is on the cruise!]
"This is where I'll sleep."
That's what I thought.
[Can't live as a pauper a second time]
No matter what happens, I must become a prince.
[That's not happening!]
I was on the "Great Escape".
[That prince title is mine]
I'm Captain SHIN!
[First game]
Then, we'll begin
[Dynamic Vision Round]
the first event!
[Using your dynamic vision,]
10.00.
[press the button at the 10-second mark]
Oh, we have to hit it then.
- But it has to be 10.00?
- Yes.
[Stop the timer]
There…Oh, exactly?
[at exactly 10 seconds to succeed]
You need to hit it exactly.
The people who succeed
will get a number each.
[Staff] Press the red button to start,
and the green button to reset.
[Red = Start]
[Green = Reset]
Here, like this and like this!
Okay, okay! I got it.
[Dynamic Vision]
DAWN.
[DAWN's 10-second timer challenge]
This is…
Ready!
[For games like this]
Rhythm is key!
Oh, that's right.
I'll do it.
Challenge accepted!
1.
[Rude]
[He's just finger-pointing]
6.
[Will the finger-pointing work?]
7. 8.
9.
10.
[Did he succeed on the first try?]
Wow, wow, what?
9.95 seconds.
[Only 0.05 seconds off]
Okay, 9.95 seconds.
Ugh…
[Not bad for a first attempt]
Nice job.
Oh, it was good.
JOHNNY.
[Second challenger, JOHNNY]
Let's go!
Oh, this…
1.
[Grooving with his whole body]
[Following JOHNNY and practicing]
4.
5.
- 6.
[Confuse him]
Say different numbers.
Different numbers.
9.
[Evil]
12.
Wow!
[Is it…]
[A success?]
Wow!
10.
JOHNNY, what is this?
Really?
(How is this possible?)
Wow, what?
Hold on.
[JOHNNY passes the 10-second timer challenge!]
Seriously?
No, like…
[Jealous]
You've got a good rhythm, JOHNNY.
You gotta stay on beat.
DAWN, you were right.
[I also stayed on the beat…]
I shouldn't have said it.
[Jealous]
Wow, JOHNNY already got a number.
[One of the three lock numbers is?]
We'll give you the number.
Oh.
[Lock number 0 secured]
0.
- I have to write it down.
- You have to memorize it.
If it's like this,
JISUNG and I will
[The pauper's nightmare is coming back]
get anxious again.
Here I go.
[Next challenger, YOHAN]
Okay, YOHAN's up!
Challenge accepted!
1.
2.
3.
4.
[Distraction]
YOHAN doesn't have much rhythm.
6.
[Unfazed]
7.
8.
9.
Ding!
He pressed the wrong one!
- He pressed the wrong one!
Agh! This is right!
[Reset]
No, no, no!
It's really right!
- No, you pressed the reset button.
- It's really right!
[What's happening here?]
No, you pressed the reset button.
Hold on.
[Before starting the 10-second timer challenge]
Press red to start and stop.
- Press green to reset.
- Oh, like this here
[Press green when resetting]
Here, like this and like this!
Okay, okay! I got it
[Definitely heard and confirmed]
9.
Ding!
[Reset button]
He pressed the wrong button.
[Q. Why did you do that?]
I know…
Yeah, why did I do that?
Well, I mean…
I thought stop was green,
and reset was red.
[Blank stare]
- No, you pressed the reset button.
- It's really right!
[Someone else's mistake is my joy]
You pressed the reset button.
[Unfair.]
No, you hit the reset button.
It's really right!
You pressed the reset button.
[Calm down, Reset Man]
No, no!
You pushed the reset button.
[Unable to easily calm down]
It's the green button, right?
- No, it's the red one.
- This is really…
0 seconds.
This is…
Red is start, green is reset.
0 seconds.
YOHAN, 0 seconds.
Eliminated, eliminated.
You did it wrong.
Hey.
[Love you]
Get lost.
Oh, really?
If it weren't for YOHAN…
I would've been
in big trouble, too.
[A meaningful sacrifice]
Can I just not play this game
and try to crack
the lock combo myself?
[Overpowered by bravado]
I feel like I can
figure it out for some reason.
[Next challenger, SHINDONG]
Here I go.
Start!
Let's go!
Oh, he's staying still.
He's so chill.
[No need for rhythm for the dancing machine]
As expected!
I'm honestly great
at things like this.
Weirdly enough,
I have a sense for this.
Click.
- Agh!
- It's the same! 9.77 seconds!
[No sense, just confidence...]
9.77 seconds.
Agh…
[JISUNG's turn]
Alright, JISUNG.
I'll start now.
I thought, "No matter what,
I have to become a prince."
[NCT DREAM’s main dancer]
I have to become a prince today.
[I'll show you my rhythm!]
Wow!
[Missed it by 0.03 seconds]
9.97 seconds.
- 0.03.
- Everyone's so good.
The young guys
are definitely better.
Alright, 44-year-old!
[The not-so-young guy is up next]
[The not-so-young guy is ready]
Okay, start!
- 1. 2.
- Pressing that will reset it!
- You have to press the green!
- 3.
4.
Pressing that will reset it!
LEETEUK, pick the right button.
[Evil distraction tactics]
AGH!!!
Not even close, right?
- 9.88 seconds.
Oh, we only have one number so far.
The game's over.
[Staff] The first attempt
of the first game has ended.
[Only JOHNNY got a number]
I told you it'll keep repeating, right?
- We'll move to the second event.
- Oh, okay, okay.
The second event is…
[Second game: Body fat burning]
the body fat burning game.
The backward run.
[The first person to run backwards]
The winner will get a number, no matter what.
[and cross the finish line wins]
How do we run here?
From there to here.
[About 15 meters]
I'm wearing dress shoes, though.
There's a taekwondo boy here.
[Leap]
Wow, you're so light.
[Already full of confidence]
I thought you were a feather
[So no one gets hurt]
It's important not to bump into each other.
- YOHAN.
- Yes.
YOHAN, let's not step on the line.
[Extremely sensitive over a single line]
Let's not step on the line.
Oh, so sensitive.
LEETEUK,
you're being so sensitive.
[I have to win to get on that cruise…!]
Hey, we're sensitive right now!
[Ready for the second game]
Ready!
[The winner of
the backward run challenge]
[will get a lock number,
no matter what!]
[Who will get the lock number?]
[While everyone runs fiercely]
(Plodding along)
Hey, hey! Be careful! Be careful!
[A lonely battle]
Hey, be careful!
[Who came in first?]
Yeah! I won!
[First place]
Honestly, it's me.
It's JOHNNY again.
- I think I came in first.
- No, it was JOHNNY.
The VAR result is…!
- The result!
- Wow!
One leg swiftly came in first…
Oh…
[Is it YOHAN
who doesn't have a number yet?]
[Or will JOHNNY pull ahead?]
[The result is…?]
[VAR]
[Video Review]
[YOHAN's foot
approaches the finish line]
[JOHNNY's leg slips in]
[JOHNNY's foot touches the ground]
[YOHAN's foot is still in the air]
[With his leg stretched out,
JOHNNY takes 1st place]
[JOHNNY gets another lock number]
JOHNNY!
Wow, JOHNNY, today…!
[JOHNNY's on the fast track to being a prince]
Wow, JOHNNY's so good.
[Sigh...]
So good.
JOHNNY, nice!
[Staff]
I'll tell you the second number.
The second number is
[Got the second lock number: 5]
5.
0, 5.
[Sharp]
When's your birthday…?
It's February 9th.
Not even close.
[Oops]
I have a feeling
I'm sleeping outside tonight.
[No one but JOHNNY got a number]
I'm suddenly feeling nervous.
- I don't have a good feeling.
- I'm anxious.
[Third game: Memory]
The next event is a memory game.
Okay, nice!
My memory's been slipping lately.
[Staff] I have some wedding invitations
from our company employees.
- Oh!
- Yes.
[After memorizing the invitation info for 1 minute,]
We'll show you the invitations for 1 minute.
[answer the prepared questions]
Alright, for 1 minute.
[This was done with full consent]
Just memorize and answer the questions we ask.
[and active help in creating the questions]
Oh, nice.
[Staff] From numbers 1 to 6,
you'll decide the order to play.
[The luck of the question order is important]
This game involves a bit of luck.
- Because we already have the questions.
- That makes sense.
Yeah, that's right.
[The questions and the order are set]
It's all about which section you focused on and memorized.
[Memorization section + Order + Difficulty = all important]
It's a battle of whether cramming works or not.
Alright, let's reveal it.
1 minute starts now!
[Memory game]
[They start memorizing the wedding invitations]
[Narration: Lee Hyerim (Bride)]
"My dream became your future,"
"and we became a beautiful
pair of birds following each other."
"After meeting each other
and dreaming of a future,"
"on this fifth spring,"
"we will lean on
each other's shoulders"
"and soar high together
as a strong pair."
"If you'll bless us
with your precious presence,"
"we'll cherish your blessings
in our hearts with gratitude forever."
[G Floor]
[Subway]
[Exit 3-1]
[Exit 5]
[Shuttle bus]
[In front of Exit 3]
[Parking]
[Packed with information]
[Saturday, March 21st, 5 PM]
[Address: SB Tower G Floor, Square,
Dosan-daero, Gangnam-gu]
Close them up!
Ugh, I didn't see everything.
This is driving me crazy.
Please decide the order.
Shall we play rock-paper-scissors?
Agh, I forgot it!
Let's just do
the order from before.
[Keeping the same order from the previous game]
From earlier, yes.
I'll go first.
I forgot everything.
[Completely forgot already]
What did you memorize?
Ugh, what did I memorize?
[Everyone's getting anxious]
Let's hurry before we forget.
So, let's just…
[Let's start before we forget]
Should we just start with DAWN?
Sure, let's just do it.
Hurry, hurry, hurry.
- Here's the first question.
- Yes.
What did
the bride and groom prepare…
Huh?
…and what did they decline?
Oh, I saw this!
[Seems like YOHAN memorized this part]
This was on there?
I saw it!
- They prepared something?
- Yes! They prepared something!
[The person playing
doesn't seem to know]
[Shocked]
We were supposed to look on the right, too?
They prepared something?
[Oh, whatever]
They prepared a house!
- Right, they have to get a house.
- Nice, they're gonna live well.
[It's over for DAWN]
What did they do?
[Forget it]
Did they decline having kids?
[Avoiding]
Oh…
I really have no idea.
Voluntary DINK.
I didn't even know it was there!
I didn't even see it.
[Wrong!]
Sorry, that's incorrect.
- Okay, next!
- This is driving me crazy.
Didn't they decline flower wreaths?
That's right.
Ugh, DAWN!
So…what?
Okay.
So, what did they prepare?
[No clue about that]
I don't know that one.
[Correct answer:
Snacks & flower wreaths]
(Slowly)
Who'd like to go second?
JOHNNY.
Sure... I'll give it a shot.
- Oh, it was there. It was on the right side.
- Okay, JOHNNY's turn.
[Next question!]
This couple
[Q. How long did this couple date?]
dated for how…
5 years!
Oh, I knew this one!
- Oh, this…!
- I should've done this one!
[Fifth spring = 5 years]
[The question everyone memorized]
It was their fifth…What was it?
Wow, JOHNNY got it right.
He got it right.
JOHNNY's was too easy.
Luck is on his side.
It's JOHNNY's day today.
[Lucky JOHNNY]
Oh, JOHNNY's done!
[cleared every
single game in one shot]
[Confirmed as the first prince]
Honestly, it's me.
The couple dated for how…
5 years.
[Luck is also a skill at this point]
Oh, JOHNNY's done!
Alright, JOHNNY.
[JOHNNY's current numbers: 0, 5]
Here's the next number.
[JOHNNY's current numbers: 0, 5, 9]
9.
[Got all his lock numbers]
Goodbye, everyone.
[5 members with no numbers at all]
This doesn't make sense.
I'm in trouble.
I might not be a prince today.
JOHNNY clinched it too early,
so I was annoyed.
[Super motivated after seeing]
I got super determined
[JOHNNY's about to climb the social ladder]
to do whatever it takes.
[As JOHNNY approaches a status upgrade]
YOHAN, go.
- YOHAN will go next.
- Yes.
[Next challenger, YOHAN]
The wedding venue of this couple…
What floor is it on?
[The answer is G Floor]
[Answer: G Floor]
Oh, I know this.
[Suddenly, everyone remembers]
I really know this!
I know it, too.
[Flared nostrils]
YOHAN doesn't know.
That place…
The basement is the parking lot.
- 3.
- If you go up…
- 2.
- Wasn't it around the 5th floor?
5th floor, wrong!
- Yeah.
- The letter is kinda similar.
Yeah, it was kinda similar.
[Self-proclaimed Brain SHINDONG goes next]
Challenge accepted!
Here it is.
The wedding venue's
main contact number…
What are the last four digits?
[Very difficult
information to memorize]
SHINDONG, I know this one!
[You memorized this??]
I know this one!
I memorized this!
What is this?
[0928]
"Permanent teeth."
Wrong!
That's the main number
for the dentist's office.
Was it 5007?
[Staff] 5007 is correct.
Right? 5007!
I memorized this.
Aw, it was G Floor.
The letter G.
[They knew each other's answers]
Oh, G Floor.
[Meanwhile, JOHNNY is in a battle of his own]
5, 9, 0.
5.
[JOHNNY's lock number combo]
0.
9.
5.
[Who's up next?]
Go for it, JISUNG
[Flailing]
[JISUNG's turn]
I'll give it a shot.
Here we go.
Challenge accepted.
If you're riding
the shuttle bus to the venue…
- I know this one.
- Oh, me too!
If you're riding the shuttle bus…
I know this one.
Oh, me too!
WHAT?!
Which exit of Gangnam-gu Office Station
should you get on at?
Just guess!
Exit 7!
(Why would he do this?)
Which exit?
Exit 7!
[JISUNG, nope!]
Exit 7, wrong!
Nice!
It's Exit 1, Exit 1.
- It's Exit 3.
[Beaming]
Please, let it be
something I looked at.
[Walk 10 minutes from Exit 3-1 of
Gangnam-gu Office Station (Line 7 & Bundang Line)]
Please.
I'm LEETEUK, your wedding MC expert.
[Wedding MC LEETEUK's turn]
I've emceed over 150 weddings.
Oh! A wedding MC expert!
That's right!
The groom's name is Lee Jaewoong.
Yes.
And the bride's name is Lee Hyerim.
Right, I memorized this.
I knew at least this much.
- Alright, then…
- Yes.
Whose father is Lee Jaesoo?
He's the bride's father!
Correct!
Wow!
He was a very "Jaesoo" (lucky) man!
Sir! Are you doing well?
It was one or the other…
Mr. Jaesoo!
[Scratches]
He just needed to guess one or the other.
What a bummer.
- LEETEUK.
- Yes.
LEETEUK,
I'll give you one lock number.
Alright, great.
[Got the lock number 4]
4.
Oh, I'm 44!
Fo-fo-forty-four!
[Ignoring]
JOHNNY, you haven't
unlocked it yet, right?
[He unlocked it!]
Finally!
[Prince JOHNNY confirmed]
Oh, nice!
[Only 2 prince spots left]
Oh…
There aren't many spots left now.
There are only two spots left.
The game's over.
It's over…Ugh.
[Reflexes: Ping-Pong challenge]
Ping Pong!
Ping-pong!
With a ping-pong paddle,
[The person who bounces the ping-pong ball]
the one who bounces the most…
[over their head the most wins]
Got it, okay
- …will get a number.
- Okay, okay!
This kind of thing is fun.
[Fixed #1]
Now, DAWN!
Hold on, this…
Objection!
Why, why, why?
I think always going first
- puts me at a disadvantage.
- That's the order we decided on earlier.
We decided on it.
[Tension spikes ahead of the new game]
I was gonna change it, but we just went with it.
- You're right.
- Okay.
[Scared]
Here we go.
Yes, I'll start.
- Fighting against the sandstorm…!
- Why is it so windy?
[The wind's blowing too]
The wind's blowing this way.
Can't I turn my back to it?
[Wind...]
Please say "Challenge accepted!"
[Start after shouting
"Challenge accepted"]
[The hyenas watch quietly]
Can I wait for the wind to stop?
No.
(Audience)
Then it might take all night!
Okay.
[Just going for it!]
Challenge accepted!
Here we go!
[1]
1.
[2]
2. That's it!
[3]
3. That's it!
[4]
4. That's it!
[Let's go! A high-spirited ping-pong dance]
3. That's it! 4. That's it!
No, but…
[Once grabbed, the red paddle doesn't stop]
Wait, I…!
7!
8!
- I can't stop right now.
- 9!
[10]
This is fun!
Nice!
[11]
11!
I want to hit it lightly!
14!
Ack!
[14]
14!
- Ack!
- 14 times!
[Got the vibes down]
I wanted to hit it lightly…!
[Currently 1st: DAWN (14 times)]
You have to do it like this.
- This is fun.
- You did well, you did.
Oh, this is fun.
[Next challenger: YOHAN]
Okay, YOHAN.
I couldn't control the power.
[It's hard to control the power…?]
(Practicing his snap)
YOHAN.
Hurry up!
It's getting dark, and we won't be able to see!
Ready?
[YOHAN's turn]
Challenge accepted!
[1]
1.
[2]
2.
- 3.
- Huh?
[REPLAY]
[Started so confidently]
1. 2.
[Sent the ping-pong ball
flying with flair]
[It's high!]
[It's too high…]
- 2.
[Plop]
3. Huh?
[Missed the target
right in front of him]
[2nd place: YOHAN (2 times)]
Because it's getting darker…
You strangely end up
hitting it harder!
YOHAN is a funny guy!
[0 points for ping-pong, 100 points for fun]
Compared to when DAWN did it,
it got a bit darker, so I couldn't see well.
[Is it because of the bangs?]
My bangs are making it hard to see…
- He's a funny guy, a really funny guy.
- So funny.
- Why are you so funny?
- Are you going to take all the broadcast time?
[New comedy star born from sandy winds]
Even if you become a pauper, you should become one like this!
[A deeply moving scene]
"Oh, you can do it like this!" and then it just dropped!
[With the burden to be funny]
Alright, here I go.
[Third challenger, SHINDONG]
SHINDONG's turn.
- Wow! I'm gonna win!
- Because this is high…!
[Light snaps despite his size]
1. 2. 3.
- Oh!
- 4 times!
3. 4.
- Oh!
- 4 times!
- Wow! I'm gonna win!
- Because this is high…!
[Once shaken, there's no turning back]
Because it's high up, it's hard.
[2nd place: SHINDONG (3 times)]
Looks like DAWN's leading
[3rd place: YOHAN (2 times)]
DAWN is currently in 1st place.
- DAWN, how many did you get?
- Please!
[Have to hit 15+ times to win a number]
14 times.
[Yesterday’s pauper
is more careful than anyone]
Alright, it’s JISUNG’s turn.
It's hard
because it goes so high.
[Unsolicited advice]
JISUNG, your bangs will really distract you.
[Let's go]
[Startled]
Oh, a bug!!!
I really don't want
to be a pauper today…
[1]
I really don't want
[2]
to be a pauper today…!
[Walking straight down the pauper lane]
[3]
3.
Waaah!!!
- 3 times! 3 times!
- Wait!
(What do I do…)
[There's no paradise
at the end of a dead end]
I was really serious about it...
Yeah, we all were serious about it.
- I think DAWN will win.
- I know, right?
[2nd place: JISUNG (3 times)]
Hey, DAWN’s gonna get a number.
[4th place: YOHAN (2 times)]
- He actually did a good job.
- I basically gave him a number.
[The ping-pong game isn't as easy as expected]
Oh, thanks, SHINDONG!
Is it hard?
- It's really hard…!!!
- No, it's fun.
Try it?
[The paupers share survival tips]
I think going backwards might be better?
You have to use this side.
Okay!
- LEETEUK, using the edge is…
- It's double-sided, so it's fine.
Ready!
[Final challenger
LEETEUK takes the stage]
[1]
1.
[2]
2.
[Taking place on the sand,]
3.
[a rhythmic gymnastics routine with a ping-pong ball]
Four
[5]
5.
[6]
6.
[Jump!]
6!
[The crowd loves it]
Wow!
[2nd place: LEETEUK (6 times)]
Okay, okay!
[3rd place: SHINDONG, JISUNG (3 times)]
Hey, this is making me dizzy!
[Why is hitting a ping-pong ball so tough?]
It's hard! And you can't really see it!
You can't really see the ball.
It's slowly getting darker.
- We have to do this again later.
- We have to do it again.
[Ping-pong game 1R winner: DAWN]
Okay, DAWN,
[DAWN's lock code]
we'll give you a number.
[DAWN's lock code: 4]
4.
[Lock Code Status]
[Prince / 1 digit / 0 digits]
Oh, but we really need
at least one number.
[Except for JOHNNY]
DAWN and I are the only ones with numbers now, right?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
[0 numbers]
At this rate, I'm gonna sleep outside.
Let's leave the table,
and just that…
[Hit at 10 seconds
returns for Round 2]
- 10 seconds.
- Alright, here I go.
- Challenge accepted!
- Let's go!
Done!
[Sabotage is a default setting]
(Swoosh)
[The green button…?]
[RESET]
- Oh?
- It's done.
[Humans repeat the same mistakes]
I was so focused on this…!
I was focused on this…!
[A wasted opportunity]
Great job.
I feel like he was doing so well.
YOHAN was getting
so excited behind you.
- He was so excited in the back.
- He got excited because you pressed green.
[No wonder I heard laughter...]
No wonder I kept hearing,
"Heh heh" behind me!
[When YOHAN messed up earlier]
He pressed the wrong one!
This is right!
[He laughed the loudest]
No, it's really right!
- No, you pressed the reset button.
- No, it's really right!
Okay, YOHAN.
[Let's stay humble]
Wow, this is driving me crazy.
This is so funny.
YOHAN, YOHAN.
- Challenge accepted!
- Let's go!
[After getting his revenge,
YOHAN goes next]
1.
2.
3.
[Feeling empty thinking about it]
4. 5.
6.
[Groovin']
7.
And 8!
And 9!
[STOP]
And 10!
- Wow!
- 9.90 seconds.
[Words from the 10-second man]
What I realized was
you shouldn't look at the numbers!
[Then what?]
Then how do you do it?
Rhythm?
So, at 8, 9, 10,
[Go with your gut feeling for 8, 9, 10]
you gotta go with your gut.
- Trust your gut?
- Yes.
[Thanks for the tip]
[SHINDONG goes next]
[Fake out]
...9!
- So close!
- 9.96 seconds.
[The sabotage is getting more and more precise]
But you even confused me!
Wow, seriously.
I got confused too.
- JISUNG's turn.
- I'll start right away.
Yeah, start right away!
Let's go!
[JISUNG's challenge]
3.
2.
[3x2=6]
6.
12!
[Please, I beg of you]
[STOP]
Oh, 9.95 seconds.
9.95 seconds.
Ugh..! I'm regressing...
I'm not sleeping
alone tonight, right?
[Bored]
That's kinda scary.
You need to shout
the numbers louder.
1!
[Shouting]
2!
3!
4!
[The timer seems intimidated]
AGH!!!!!
[Did that energy work?]
[Unfortunately, everyone failed]
[Let's move on]
Okay, next game please.
We'll go to the next game.
If we keep failing…
The backward run?
we're gonna run out of
wedding invitations.
[The backward run again]
YOHAN might actually win this round.
I keep losing this one.
SHINDONG, you stay right by YOHAN.
No elbows allowed!
Block YOHAN.
[Openly getting in
each other’s way]
[Backward run]
[1st place gets a lock code, no matter what]
- How are we supposed to do this?
- It's way too hard.
How is everyone doing this…?
It's scary.
[Only one person gets a number...!]
I really…
don't wanna be a pauper today.
You can't look back.
- LEETEUK!
- Yeah?
[Pauper solidarity]
I'm only cheering for you, LEETEUK…!
[Touched]
Nice! Pauper!
Pauper!
- Let's go!
[Yesterday's paupers]
Pauper!
[united with pure grit]
JISUNG, we have to do well.
I'll really do my best.
[And yesterday's princes, dreaming of more glory]
We had a tough time yesterday.
Everyone, please run carefully!
- Yes!
- Look forward as you run!
[READY]
Get ready!
We have to win
[We promised to be princes together…!]
no matter what tomorrow.
[Running backwards
on the path to a higher status!]
[Start!]
[Scampering]
How are you supposed to run fast like this?
LEETEUK!
How are you
supposed to run fast like this?
LEETEUK!
How are you
supposed to run fast like this?
Whoa!
(Ran without looking back)
[Crash]
Whoa!
[YOHAN took a hard hit]
Oh, it's me!
It's me!
He got blocked over there! He got blocked!
I think it's me!
- Hold on!
- I think it's me!
[An unexpected incident]
- YOHAN hit the corner!
- Hold on, hold on!
[Lingering impact]
Hey, YOHAN hit the corner!
Are you okay?
[In the mood to be alone]
Hey, YOHAN.
YOHAN hit the corner!
Are you okay?
[Murmuring, not knowing how to comfort him]
I'm okaaay...
- You're okay?
- It's kind of…
[Fortunately, nothing too deep…]
- Was it a slight in and out?
- Yes.
Oof.
But really…
[Witness report]
He ran without looking back.
[The one who doesn't turn back]
That's how you run fast!
[claims victory]
I'll always be last for this one.
[Hold up]
YOHAN was
the favorite to win.
Right.
- But because he got hit there…!!
- Right.
He couldn't even
cross the finish line!
Did anyone see?
[The winner is YOHAN or LEETEUK?!]
Trust me, it was me!
Did anyone see?
I saw it!
Come on,
I crossed it and popped back out.
Nope.
Now.
Nope, YOHAN got caught here.
[LEETEUK's claim]
[1. YOHAN collided with the desk]
At that exact moment, JISUNG
[2. JISUNG stopped, thinking YOHAN stopped]
kind of stopped, because he thought YOHAN crossed it.
Yeah, yeah, I did stop.
- Right? So he stopped.
- I stopped.
Oh, it's me!
It's me!
[3. LEETEUK crossed the line at that moment]
And I crossed the line! Really!
The reason is…
[Continuing with YOHAN's counterargument]
If I didn't cross, then I didn't.
[He crossed the line with his butt]
But I did, so I crossed it!
No! You once…! No!
No, seriously!
I saw it from here.
[A tense standoff]
After getting stabbed, you paused!
You paused and went, "Oh!"
- No, I kinda crossed it.
- No, seriously.
[Revealing the VAR results]
It's there, it's there!
I saw it!
The results are out! It's out!
Who is it?
[YOHAN was ahead]
[YOHAN's leg is in]
[YOHAN wins by a hair]
Oh!
Did YOHAN cross it?
Oh? He crossed it!
- Yeah, I went in! This is right!
- Oh, he went in!
Where, where, where, where?
YOHAN crossed it.
[In denial]
He crossed the line with his butt and the table.
The desk went in, too.
They all crossed it.
(Audience)
[Lingering disappointment]
Did he go in?
He was the first to go in.
Did his foot go in?
Yeah.
[Hehe]
Oh, he's in. Fine, fine!
[Lingering regret]
Oh, that's so odd!
Both legs went in!
[Fought through the injury]
[YOHAN wins the backward run]
Wow.
YOHAN, get your number.
- YOHAN.
- Yes.
[YOHAN's Passcode]
Only you and I have no numbers.
[YOHAN's Passcode: 7]
7.
- 7.
[Current Lock Status]
[Prince / 1 number / 0 number]
[Round 2: Invitation memorization]
We'll give you the invitations.
Here's the second wedding couple.
Wow, this place…
[Prosperity]
So many people got married!
Thank you.
Does Seogu live in Busan?
[1-minute invitation memorization, start!]
Ready, go!
[Narration: Kim Seogu (Groom)]
"On a blossoming spring day in April,"
"the two of us
are tying the knot."
"We promise to live
a life full of love and harmony."
"We would be grateful
for your presence to bless us."
"Seogu, the eldest son of
Kim Jutaek and Kwon Mija."
"Mina, the second daughter of
Jeong Geolchae and Park Soonhee."
"Saturday,
April 4th, 2026, at 2 PM."
"Tower Convention,
2nd Floor, Grand Ballroom."
[Shuttle Bus: Exit 4]
[15-minute walk from Exit 2]
[Shuttle Bus: Exit 5]
[Every 15 minutes]
[Parking available for 1400 cars]
[As expected,
a ton of info to memorize]
[The first invitation]
Oh, earlier…
[The audience is bored]
They declined flower wreaths.
Right?
It's written right here.
[I'm on edge, don't bother me]
Stop, stop.
[Staff] 10 seconds left.
Why isn't it sinking in?
[STOP]
Close it, please.
[Will their cramming succeed?]
It's time to test
your luck with cramming!
[First challenger]
Who's up first?
[YOHAN]
I'll go!
- YOHAN, let's go.
- Yes.
How many cars
can the parking lot hold?
[Memorized this one]
Oh, I know this one!
Too easy!
Oh, I'm gonna lose it!
YOHAN, just go for it!
[A question that basically gives him a room]
They're just giving you a room.
I seriously looked at it
up to "If coming by car."
Just guess!
Guess, YOHAN, just guess!
I'd love for you to sleep on board.
[Everyone knows except him]
YOHAN.
- 3
- 1000...!!!
1200???
Oh wow, amazing!
The answer is 1400 cars.
Wow!
[Instant elimination]
[Second challenger]
We'll go to the next one.
Who's next?
Me!
[DAWN bravely steps up]
DAWN, let's go.
Challenge accepted!
When coming by car…!
I'll give you 4 syllables.
Taek, Geol, Ju, Chae.
I know this, I know!
[Why is someone else's question always easier?]
With these four syllables,
create the names
of the fathers on both sides.
[Stress]
Hey, you don't know this?
Taek, Geol, Ju, Chae.
The order doesn't matter.
[Stressed, because they know]
Taek, Geol, Ju, Chaek?
[That might come off as a little rude]
Ju, Chae.
- What?
- Ju, Chae.
- Ju, Chae?
- Yeah, like Chae for "vegetables."
[Frustrated]
- Mr. Jutaek!
- 4.
[And...?]
[Hesitant]
Fail.
[Puzzled]
Why would you…
- You just said it all!
- The four syllables, just now…
Oh, but I forgot what they were.
[A brain freeze moment]
What was it after that?
What was it again?
Geol.
Isn't it Geolchae?
- Challenge accepted!
- Oh…
- Let's go.
- I'm going crazy.
[SHINDONG's third attempt]
Okay, third question.
Oh!
[Staff]
It's a transportation question.
I memorized
the transportation stuff.
[Staff] This wedding venue
offers shuttle buses
accessible from
two subway stations.
Right, right.
Which subway station
provides a shuttle at Exit 5?
- Right! I know this one!
- I know this.
- 5.
Gasan Digital Complex Station.
- Correct!
- That's correct.
Wow!
- Oh wow.
- Right, Guro Station was Exit 4.
It was Guro and Gasan.
[SHINDONG leaves the 0-number club]
He finally got one.
- Wow.
- JISUNG!
[Suddenly, JISUNG is in last place alone]
Let's go!
- Okay, here's SHINDONG's number.
- Okay.
[SHINDONG's passcode: 3]
SHINDONG's number is 3.
3.
What was my number again...?
[YOHAN, you're really funny]
It isn't over, right?
Your number's 2!
Don't lie!
(Got a number, but forgot it)
Seriously, what was it?
(Still didn't get one)
YOHAN, it was 2.
[Currently, the 0-number duo]
Next up, JISUNG!
How often do the shuttle buses run
at this wedding venue?
- Oh, I know this.
- I know this too!
[Desperate]
I really know this, I do!
I…
15 minutes!
Correct!
JISUNG, that was good.
[Nice, legendary!]
Challenge accepted…!
But didn't everything come out already?
Okay, your number is
[JISUNG's passcode: 8]
8.
Okay, thank you.
[Current status of invitation questions]
Everything's already been said.
[SHINDONG and JISUNG succeeded]
I feel comforted.
Did you hear
what my number was earlier?
[Awkward]
Yours?
3?!
- I think someone had a 3…
- I'm going crazy.
Did you really forget?
[Serious]
Yeah.
I'm going crazy.
- Here's your question, LEETEUK.
- Yes.
- Between the groom…
- and the bride,
- Yes.
who is the second-born?
[Haha!]
There was something like that?
The bride!!!
Huh?
[The bride is]
She's the second daughter...!
The groom is the first son.
[Second daughter]
Wow, he's really good.
Oh, I didn't know this.
Everyone, I am the master MC!
[Proud]
I memorize scripts in no time.
[Respect]
He's really the ultimate
- wedding MC!
- Oh, he's emceed a lot.
[Confidence from experience]
I sure have.
[LEETEUK's passcode]
LEETEUK, I'll give you your 2nd number.
[LEETEUK's passcode: 8]
8!
Okay, one more to go.
[Current lock code status]
[Prince / 2 numbers / 1 number]
Let's go!
- This is my game.
- Yes.
[Ping-Pong game returns for Round 2]
Okay, challenge accepted!
[1]
1!
- I can't see it! I really can't!
- 2!
- 3!
- He can't see!
- 4!
- He can't see it, he can't.
[The Ping-Pong King's steady steps]
5!
[As long as there's ping-pong, I'm a prince again today...!]
6!
- 7!
- Wow, DAWN, you're really good!
- 8!
- Hey, he's winning with just ping-pong!
9!
10!
What's with this guy!
[Out]
11…10!
[DAWN did it 10 times]
10 in a row.
Wow, but you really can't see it!
You can't see it, you can't.
[Second challenger, YOHAN]
Challenge accepted!
Oh, he's so funny already.
- 1!
[Taekwondo Boy's lively steps]
2!
- 3!
- Nice!
What's with the steps?
Agh! This is driving me crazy!
[Swinging in the air]
If I didn't grab my hat!
His steps…
They're Taekwondo steps!
[YOHAN does it 3 times again]
You always do it 3 times!
Wow, but I really can't see!
You can't see it!
You really can't!
[Third challenger, SHINDONG]
SHINDONG is next.
- Challenge accepted!
- 10 is max right now.
- I'm gonna get another number here.
- 1!
[2]
2!
[3]
3!
- 4!
- You're doing great!
- Nice!
- 5!
[Keeping a steady pace]
6!
Oh, wait a second.
- The lights are on!
- 8!
[9]
9!
[10]
10!
- Oh, this is cheating!
- 11!
[SHINDONG, in his ping-pong element]
12! 13!
[14]
14!
[15]
15!
- Oh, I can't see it.
- 16!
[A new ping-pong record]
17!
[18]
18!
- 19!
- Wow!
- 20!
- Wow! What?
- 21!
- AGH!
[SHINDONG sets a new record with 21 hits]
Okay! That's good! That's good enough!
[Currently 1st place: Shindong (21 times)]
Aw, this is my game…
[2nd place: Dawn (10 times)]
That's good enough, that's good enough.
Okay, okay, this is good enough.
[The fourth challenger, JISUNG]
4 hits.
1!
2!
[Not again…]
3!
Where are you going,
where are you going?
[2]
2!
[Habitual charging]
3!
Where are you going,
where are you going?
[4]
Where are you going, where are you going?
[5]
JISUNG, where are you going?
5!
[Frustrated]
If it weren't for this...!
[Regrets...]
- JISUNG, are you okay?
- Silly JISUNG.
[Last challenger, LEETEUK]
[1]
[2]
2!
[Drop]
Hey JISUNG.
- The wind blows it over there.
- Right? Right?
[Let's all blame the wind]
It's not by choice for me either!
That's exactly
when the wind blows a lot!
[Round 2]
The timing…!
[SHINDONG wins the ping-pong game]
This is a game of luck!
- So funny.
- Okay!
[SHINDONG's passcode]
SHINDONG's second number is
[SHINDONG's passcode: 7]
7!
[The sun slowly goes down]
Oh, okay.
Okay.
- Okay, okay.
- This is fun.
[Current lock code status]
LEETEUK and SHINDONG have 2 numbers.
[Nowhere near getting all the numbers]
DAWN, YOHAN, and JISUNG have 1 number each.
[Staff]
We're running out of time,
so we're gonna
cut down the number of games.
Sounds good.
Yes, yes.
We'll remove the backward run.
- Yes.
- Oh, okay!
Okay, nice!
The one thing
I could win is gone.
The one thing I could win…!
If it gets removed…
I was gonna
cross the finish line again.
[Next game: 10-second timer]
Okay.
- Let's go right away.
- Let's do this!
Oh, silly me.
[DAWN’s challenge]
I'll do it now! Challenge accepted!
Let's go!
[As DAWN concentrates,]
[all kinds of noises
are heard from behind]
[United as one
for the sake of sabotage]
Dum-ba-ddu, dum-ba-ddu!
Ideunikka mmm!
[Beatboxing on this side]
Dopamine!
U-ji-ju-ju-u-ji-ju!
[Only focused
on the rhythm of my heart]
[But will it work?]
Oh!
9.94 seconds.
[Sabotage accomplished]
Oh, okay!
9.94 seconds.
Your turn, YOHAN.
Here I go.
[Next up, challenger, YOHAN]
YOHAN's turn.
[Challenge accepted]
2.
3.
[Beatbox boy is back]
- 4.
- Hit it.
- 5.
- 6.
- Hit it.
- 7.
8.
- 6. 7. 8…
- Hit it. Hit it. Hit it.
[Let's go, YOHAN!]
Now!
[Success?!]
Wow!
Now!
AGH!!!
Wow, amazing!
[Flailing in frustration]
Wow! Wow!
(Legendary)
10.01 seconds!
[Failed by 0.01 seconds]
Wow…
- That was so close.
- You're insane!
[Next up, SHINDONG]
Let's go!
SHINDONG.
[Currently have 2 numbers]
SHINDONG, if you win here, you go straight on board.
[If he succeeds, he's confirmed as a prince]
Right.
Be the prince!
Prince SHINDONG!
- It's coming.
- Hit it!
[Will the second prince be crowned?!]
Now! Now!!
- Now! Now!!
- Hit it!
Ugh…I totally missed it.
It's not even close.
[0% Regret]
I'll start right away.
[Beatbox Boy's Challenge]
Right away…
JISUNG's turn!
I'm going to become a prince,
no matter what!
[Will JISUNG
get closer to prince status?]
Hit it now!
[And the result is…?!]
Ack, no!
9.97 seconds.
I keep stopping it there!
[Round 1:9.97 seconds]
9.97 seconds.
[Round 2:9.95 seconds]
Oh, 9.95 seconds.
[Round 3:9.97 seconds]
Oh, 9.97 seconds.
I'm usually
good at stuff like that.
But,
I kept missing it by 0.03 or 0.05 seconds,
so it was very frustrating.
[Just hovering around the target]
I keep stopping it there!
It wasn't this vibe.
[LEETEUK with 2 numbers goes next]
[If he succeeds,
he'll become a prince]
(Please fail)
[Will he escape pauper status?]
- Challenge accepted!
- Let's go!
Just watch.
1!!
2!!
3!!
1!!
[His loud chant echoes over the Nile River]
2!! 3!! 4!!
- That's it.
- Oh!
[And the drill sergeant's result is?]
6!! 7!! 8!!
9!! 10!!
OH!!!
So pointless.
9!! 10!!
OH!!!
So pointless.
I don't even regret it.
[Just a person with a sore throat]
No regret at all.
Take this out.
But LEETEUK,
you know you pressed the button
and then shouted 10?
9!!
(Pressed first)
10!!
OH!!!
So pointless!
[Next game: Invitation memorization]
Now, here’s the third invitation.
So many people get married
at this company!
Yeah, so many are getting married.
But like…
I can't see the letters well.
[The sky grows darker]
I can't see the letters well!
I can't see it.
[Under the same conditions
as Han Seokbong]
Okay, start!
[The invitation memorization begins!]
[Narration: Lee Wongi (Groom)]
"Wongi and Jeongmin are getting married."
"Lee Wongi, the son of
Lee Byeongchun and Lee Inhee."
"Heo Jeongmin, the daughter of
Heo Jun and Park Suji."
"September 14, 2025."
(Temporal lobe stimulation)
"Sunday, at 2 PM."
"Convention, 3rd Floor, Royal Hall."
[2 hours of free parking,
then 1,500 KRW per 30 minutes]
2 hours free.
This will definitely be a question.
[Who will answer correctly
and receive a lock number?]
[Time's up]
Please close it.
[First challenger]
Who'd like to go first?
[DAWN]
Me!
DAWN, let's go.
Oh, I couldn't memorize it.
My brain's not working.
Alright, here's the first question.
Yes.
What is the name of the wedding hall
where this couple got married?
Oh!
What is the name of the wedding hall
where this couple got married?
(He must know the answer)
Oh!
Royal Hall.
Wow.
Correct!
It wasn't Conventional Hall?
[YOHAN, you're really, really funny]
So funny! YOHAN, you're so funny.
YOHAN's so good at this.
YOHAN is so funny.
You should just sleep outside tonight.
[DAWN's second lock number]
DAWN, I'll give you your number.
- 6.
- Okay!
[2 numbers: LEETEUK, SHINDONG, DAWN]
You have 2 now?
[1 number: YOHAN, JISUNG]
Yes, I have 2.
Here's the next question.
[Raises hand]
Yes.
- I'll go next.
- JISUNG's up.
Oh, nice!
[JISUNG goes next
before he forgets]
[Just had to be the hardest question]
You got a really difficult question.
Oh…
But someone mentioned this earlier.
[It was mentioned earlier?]
Oh?
But someone mentioned this earlier.
- Oh? It's that.
- Huh?
Here’s the question.
(I will get this right, no matter what)
If you attended this wedding and parked for 3 hours,
how much would the parking fee be?
[A sudden math problem]
Oh, this one's tough.
- How much would the parking fee be?
- Oh, this is so easy.
Oh, this one's tough.
I asked about this.
"This is gonna come out."
[2 hours of free parking,
then 1,500 KRW per 30 minutes]
[YOHAN had a hunch about this]
1,500 won per 30 minutes.
[JISUNG also saw it]
1,500 won?
[Q. What's the parking fee for 3 hours?]
[2 hours free, so 1 hour charge]
[1,500 won for every 30 minutes]
[1,500 won x 2 = 3,000 won]
- Oh, this is so hard.
- It’s just simple math.
[He can get it right
if he just does some mental math]
I saw this earlier...
W…Wait!
[You said you saw it!]
What do you mean, "Wait"?
Seriously, wait!
This…This…Why…
- Wow, hold on!
- 5.
[His mind is blank from anxiety]
Wow, I vaguely remember this.
- Oh, what do I do…!
- 3.
- 1.
- 1,500 won?
Wrong!
What was it again?
[YOHAN who swore he saw it]
I asked about this. "This is gonna come out!"
[Wrong again]
2,400 won!
- No, no!
- Why?
What are you talking about?
It's 1,500 won for 30 minutes,
so 3,000 won.
Correct!
[SHINDONG, the only one on the team]
Wow, so close!
[that can do basic math]
It's free for 2 hours.
Oh! 2 hours are free!
[Regret overload]
Ugh, so annoying…!
[With this momentum]
Let's move on to the next question.
[SHINDONG moves in]
Who? SHINDONG?
- Challenge accepted.
- Let's go!
[Current lock code situation]
[Prince / 2 numbers / 1 number]
[If he succeeds,
he can become a prince!]
[Will he become a prince?]
Here's your question.
What is the government office
near this wedding venue?
- Huh?
- A government office?
What is the government office
near this wedding venue?
- Huh?
- A government office?
- Where would you "paste" it?
- Paste what where?
[Just switching to comedy mode now]
I didn't see this one.
[Only the former paupers are serious]
I have absolutely no clue.
What is a "government office"?
[What is a "government office"?]
[Any institutions that handle
specific duties to run the government]
(For example,
the Ministry of Education, the Ministry of Justice, ...)
[The Ministry of Defense]
[Is SHINDONG]
No, it's just
[a human calculator or a memory master?]
Not the old neighborhood office, but what do they call it now?
[Answer: Ministry of Defense]
The community center.
Oh, I know this!
- Oh, community center.
- 5.
Wrong!
I have no idea.
Not the district office,
but what do they call it now?
Oh, I know this!
It's near my house!
[He lives near
the Ministry of Defense?]
- Oh, really?
- Yeah.
The Yongsan District Office!
- It's not a post office.
- It's in Yongsan.
It's the Ministry of Defense.
- Oh, really?
- The Ministry of Defense!
You really acted like you knew it!
It's near my house!
The Yongsan District Office.
The Yongsan District Office!
Oh, really?
Challenge accepted!
[Fourth challenger, LEETEUK]
Oh, I didn't look at it properly.
[Currently has 2 numbers]
Here we go. This is an observation question.
[He needs to get this right to become a prince]
Yes.
So, in the photo…
There was a photo, right?
I didn't look at the photo…
- Oh, really?
- Yes.
[Predicting a failure]
I didn't look at the photo…
- Oh, really?
- Yes.
In the photo, what was around…
Yes.
…the bride's neck?
- Around the bride's neck?
- Yes.
It'd be something
like a necklace, right?
Right, it was a necklace.
Wrong!
[Forget being a prince! He's committed to being funny]
[Nothing there]
There was nothing there.
- There was nothing there.
- You're right.
No, but I couldn't see it!
[It was hard to see...]
But yeah, it's hard to see.
[Another chance to be a prince drifts away]
LEETEUK, we should've finished the game here.
I know, right?
[Last challenger, YOHAN]
Yes, challenge accepted!
- YOHAN's turn.
- Yes.
[Prince / 1 number / 2 numbers / 2 numbers / 1 number / 2 numbers]
[Staff]
This is a math problem.
(Giving up)
(The twinkle in his eye is gone)
As listed in the directions to the wedding hall,
what is the sum of
all the subway exit numbers?
How many subway stations are there?
[Staff] …Did you not look at it?
[Blinking]
[Samgakji Station Exit 12]
[Samgakji Station Exit 1]
[Namyeong Station Exit 1]
[12 + 1 + 1 = ??]
(Just say anything)
[Correct answer: 14]
20…
Wrong.
Wait a minute, then…
Is it ping-pong again?
Ping-pong?
I'm in!
[Lights ON]
Now that the lights are on,
[Hitting the ping-pong]
we'll do ping-pong again.
Alright, let's head home!
Challenge accepted!
[Currently has 2 numbers]
Okay, DAWN.
[DAWN has the highest chance to be the prince]
Let's start!
[Showing a unique sense of calmness,]
But, hold on…I…!
[he secured a number during Round 1 of ping-pong!]
DAWN, I'll give you your number. 4!
Actually, up until recently,
I've been going
to play ping-pong a lot.
Really?
I could totally do this.
[I'm the local ping-pong master]
[1]
1!
[2]
It's even harder to see the ball!
[3]
3!
[1]
1!
[Focusing on the ball through the darkness]
It's even harder to see the ball!
[Unwavering focus]
Wow, I can't see it!
[Realizing it's no laughing matter]
Oh, he's doing well.
7!
8!
9!
[9]
[10]
10!
[11]
11!
[12]
12!
[13]
13!
[Local ping-pong master indeed]
14!
[15]
15!
[16]
16!
DAWN made it through.
It's gonna be DAWN.
DAWN, stop it…
[Tap.]
18.
[Tap. Tap.]
19.
[Tap. Tap. Tap]
20.
- DAWN, stop it…
- 17.
[The never-ending]
18.
[rally with himself]
19.
[20]
20.
[Steadily broke through 20 hits]
21.
[22]
22.
He must really want a number.
[23]
23.
[24]
24.
[DAWN gets 24 hits]
- Oh, DAWN's got it.
- He's done.
[Emerging as a strong contender for 1st place]
Oh, DAWN, you've got one.
Hey, then you've got all 3, right?
- Yes.
- Oh!
Don't go near the lights.
(Checking the lights)
You can't see anything.
[Can YOHAN surpass DAWN?]
- You'll get blinded.
- Oh, it's actually worse.
Okay, YOHAN's up!
Challenge accepted!
I'm looking forward to this.
[1]
1!
[2]
2!
Why do I keep doing this? Seriously?
[Hit]
1!
[Hit, hit]
2!
Why do I keep doing this? Seriously?
[Self-loathing]
Who are you talking to?
- Whoa, whoa, whoa!
- Why are you so angry?
Who are you talking to?
Wait, wait, what's going on?
[A really distracting noise from somewhere]
Who was it earlier? That kept croaking?
[Culprit: Frog]
(Nationality: Egyptian)
But I really can't see it.
You can't see it, you can't.
I thought it was a drill!
Tta-da-da-da-dak!
It'd be going like "Tta-da-da-da-dak,"
and then suddenly go offbeat!
(Offbeat)
Tta-da-da-da-dak! And tta-da-da-da-dak!
It'd sound like that!
[Croak! Croak!]
[Ugh]
We can change the ball color?
Oh, this is hard to see…
White shows up the best.
Do you want to change it?
[SHINDONG is serious about being a prince]
White stands out the best.
[Multi-talented SHINDONG even swapped the ball!]
Oh, SHINDONG kinda makes me anxious.
He's good at this.
[Currently 1st place: DAWN (24 times)]
Wind, please blow!
[2nd place: YOHAN (2 times)]
Here I go!
[SHINDONG begins]
- 4!
- Oh, he's good.
[Steady hits]
5!
[Suddenly anxious]
Oh, nice.
Oh, wait.
This is trouble.
[Croak]
6!
7!
[Croak]
8!
[The frog returns, croaking offbeat]
Wow, that sound is really wild.
Oh, stay on beat!
[9]
9!
[Croak]
[10]
10!
[Croak]
[11]
[The frog suddenly goes off beat]
Oh, stay on beat!
Oh, come on!
[11]
[Croak]
[12]
Oh, come on!
[2nd place: SHINDONG (12 times)]
He was trying to stay on beat…
[The offbeat frog's curse]
What's wrong with that frog?
[Offbeat frog victim #1]
I told you the frog has issues!
[Offbeat frog victim #2]
Who is it? Who's there?
Ugh!!
Hey, is something there?
- Yeah, yeah.
- There's something there?
[The offbeat frog's crazy presence]
But you really can't hear anything else.
All you hear is
"Tta-da-da-da-dak! Wa-ra-ra-rak!"
The funny thing is,
it only does it when we're hitting the ball!
Yeah.
[Meanwhile, JISUNG is]
All you hear is "Tta-da-da-da-dak! Wa-ra-ra-rak!"
[firmly preparing for the mission]
The funny thing is, it only does it when we're hitting the ball!
Yeah.
Okay, JISUNG's turn!
I'll start right away!
Please, please!
(High expectations)
JISUNG's really sincere right now.
[Sincere JISUNG's challenge]
I really…
[1]
1!
[2]
2!
[Where are you going?]
Where do you keep going?
(After starting in the middle)
1!
[2]
2!
- 3!
- Where do you keep going?
[He disappears]
4!
Where are you going?
[3]
3!
[4]
4!
[JISUNG hits it 4 times]
Oh, wait a second.
[3rd place: JISUNG (4 times)]
No, but I…
I have no ping-pong talent.
Hold on.
But I have no ping-pong talent.
[It's okay, you're NCT DREAM]
Hey! Why are you all so funny?
JISUNG just drifts over there
even without the wind.
You weren't
prepared for that, huh?
I wasn't ready for it.
(Heavy footsteps)
Agh…
Is headwind better or tailwind?
[Recommending headwind]
Headwind is better.
- Headwind is better?
- Headwind is better.
Right, definitely headwind.
[Current Rankings]
How many do you have? DAWN? How many?
[1st: DAWN (24 times) / 2nd: SHINDONG (12 times)]
21 times.
[3rd: JISUNG (4 times) / 4th: YOHAN (2 times)]
24 times, 24 times.
[Will LEETEUK take the 1st place spot?]
Oh, 24 times... This is gonna be tough.
[Or will DAWN firmly keep his place on top?]
Oh…I won.
You're not
gonna run backwards, right?
[Or will the offbeat frog
just do its thing?]
Alright, challenge accepted!
[Croak]
(Croak)
You're not gonna run backwards, right?
The frog's at it again…
[Loudly foreshadowing his performance]
It started, right? That's all you'll hear.
Tap!
[Croak]
[Will he overcome the frog's croaking?]
Tap! Tap!
[Croak]
Tap!
[Starting on beat with the croaks]
1!
Tap!
[Croak]
2!
3!
[Croak]
4!
That's it!
You've got it! You've got the vibe!
[6]
6!
[He's got it, he's got the vibe]
You've got it! You've got the vibe!
- Oh! Oh!
- That's it!
- 5!
- You've got it! You've got the vibe!
[6]
6!
[7]
7!
LEETEUK, hit it!
[8]
8!
[Was doing great,
before passing it to a staff member's head]
[A happy audience]
Why are you aiming at the director's head?
Aren't you being
too obvious, LEETEUK?
Director, I'm sorry.
(That's okay)
No, like…
[DAWN gets his 3rd lock code]
DAWN, congratulations.
The third number!
Wow!
[Bummer]
[DAWN's passcode: 4, 6, 1]
1.
Wow!
[He'll be confirmed as a prince when he unlocks it]
Only one more person is left.
The people with 2 numbers
are SHINDONG and me.
[Two lock numbers: LEETEUK and SHINDONG]
The people with 2 numbers are SHINDONG and me.
[One lock number]
And YOHAN.
[YO HAN & JISUNG]
I've got one.
- One?
- I also have one.
- Oh!
- Oh, okay.
- LEETEUK.
- 1, 2! 1, 2!
Let's do it, LEETEUK.
It's either you or me.
[Desperate times for the people with 2 numbers]
SHINDONG, you can just go.
[Only one of them can be a prince here]
It's either you or me.
SHINDONG, you can just go.
Okay, YOHAN.
[Back to the 10-second timer]
Oh, but YOHAN is so funny.
- So funny, so funny.
- YOHAN.
[Basically, YOHAN's last chance]
So funny, YOHAN is so funny.
[Croak]
Shout "Challenge accepted."
Challenge accepted!
[The offbeat frog that likes YOHAN]
I think it only croaks when YOHAN's doing it.
[Croak, croak]
Come on now.
[Croak]
2!
3!
[Croak]
4!
[The frog croaks on beat every second]
But the frog's croaking every second.
(REPLAY)
2!
3!
4!
- But the frog's croaking every second.
- Oh, 6!
(Rest)
7!
8!
[Suddenly offbeat]
Oh! Don't go offbeat!
Don't go offbeat!
Oh, come on!
[The frog's relentless offbeat attack]
Don't go offbeat!
Offbeat…!
[On the verge of tears]
Offbeat…It keeps going offbeat!
[Thanks, frog]
- 9.89 seconds.
- Offbeat…It keeps going offbeat!
[Jealous]
This show belongs to YOHAN...
[Next up, SHINDONG]
Here I go.
Ready!
[The one
who must succeed this time]
[And the one who hopes he fails]
Hey, it's going offbeat.
- Was it always this fast?
- Hey, it's going offbeat.
[Will SHINDONG overcome
this offbeat curse?]
[Serious]
Hey, it's going offbeat.
[He pressed it]
[And the result?]
Oh!
Oh, but…
[Everyone's struggling because of the frogs]
But the frog bothers you more than you'd think!
No one's able to do this.
[Even though JISUNG tried confidently]
Do it like this… I'll go right away.
JISUNG's turn!
[A desperate face]
Please!
[And disappointing results]
Oh…
- 10.09 seconds.
- Oh, that was so close.
- Ugh…
- 10.09.
The only way to win is
[The turn comes back to LEETEUK]
for me to out-yell the frog!
[Croak]
That's right.
Focus.
[Croak]
1!
[LEETEUK's loud counterattack]
2!
3!
[Croak]
4!
5!
[Croak]
6!
7!
[Croak]
8!
9!
10!
AGH!!!
9.92…
This is hard, so hard.
How come
he hasn't unlocked it yet?
[Still roaming around
like a lost soul]
[DAWN's lock number combinations]
[There are only 3 possibilities...]
Oh, I forgot to press the button.
[Silly me...]
It actually takes
longer than you think.
[Urgent]
What's the next game? Ping-pong?
It's ping-pong right away?
[Staff]
We only prepared invitations for 3 rounds.
Then that's over?
[We…]
We thought we'd already
[overestimated you...]
have our 3 people by now.
Oh, okay.
Then there are
only 2 games left now?
[Only 2 out of 4 games left]
Yes, we only have 2 more games left.
Can we run backwards, though?
No, no, no, it's dangerous.
I'll cross the finish line one more time…
[Too dark, too risky]
No, no, no.
No way, no way
[With an average record of 2.333 hits, YOHAN goes again]
Challenge accepted!
(Pretty serious)
- 1!
- That's it!
- 2!
- 1!
- That's it!
- 2!
- 3!
- That's it!
(JOHNNY's luggage)
Ohhhh!!
Hey, this is seriously cheating.
Come on…
What do you
mean it's cheating?
[Responsible for
85% of the laughter]
I'm sorry... It's my fault...
["ALL or NOTHING" = YOHAN's program]
This one's on me.
[Upset]
I'm sorry.
YOHAN is such a lovable klutz.
He was seriously so funny then.
Former S-TARKING MC]
YOHAN, you're so funny.
[YOHAN, the talent that entertainers are eyeing]
It makes me wanna take care of him.
The strange thing is,
for the ping-pong game,
he starts with a hat on.
After bouncing it once or twice,
he removes his hat.
He plays like
he's using two paddles!
YOHAN, I'm so envious of you
[Currently 1st place: YOHAN (3 times)]
He's being funny
- in every possible way.
- Hey, how are you making this funny?
[And]
He hits it like this.
[And the next challenger JISUNG is…]
He was here, so it couldn't be helped.
[Round 1:3 times]
I really don’t want to be a pauper today.
[Round 2:5 times]
Where are you going, where are you going?
[An average record holder with 4 hits]
JISUNG, where are you going?
[Round 3:4 times]
Where do you keep going?
Where are you going?
[Will JISUNG have a miracle?]
Oh wait.
I really… Today…
I really want to be
a prince today.
No, you never know.
JISUNG, how about you just get it?
You have to get it!
I'll start…
I'll start right away!
[1]
1!
[2]
2!
[Heading towards pauper life]
Oh, JOHNNY!
[1] One
[2] Two
Oh, JOHNNY!
[2nd place: JISUNG (2 times)]
It's all because of JOHNNY!
[Dreams of being a prince vanish]
Should we just
give him another chance?
He just starts like this
from the beginning!
Hey, why are you so ba…
Was JISUNG always so…
I think I'm not cut out for this.
JISUNG's not good at this!
I seriously must
not be cut out for this.
[But you're in NCT DREAM]
You're angling it out to the front!
I think I'm just not cut out for this.
Agh…
I should give up...
Oh, LEETEUK!
[Finally unlocked it!]
[DAWN secures a prince spot again]
It looks like I got it again.
[DAWN / Prince twice in a row]
I think, Egypt…
I think I vibe well with Egypt.
[Only one person
can be a prince now]
[Current lock code status]
[Prince / 2 numbers / 1 number]
[Strong candidates to be a prince:
LEETEUK, SHINDONG]
["Solar Barque" / I'm gonna be a prince (again) today]
Here I go!
Okay, SHINDONG's doing it.
Let's go!
[1]
1!
[2]
2!
[Steadily moving like a pro]
Oh, SHINDONG's got it.
[4]
4!
[5]
5!
This one goes to SHINDONG.
Oh no, what do I do…?
[5]
5!
[As soon as that was said]
6!
[SHINDONG starts speeding up]
[10]
10!
[11]
11!
[12]
12!
- 13!
- Oh! Oh!
Oh!
[13]
13!
[SHINDONG hits it 13 times]
13 times!
[Currently 1st place: Shindong (13 times)]
13 times.
Oh, so close!
- You hit it 13 times.
- 13 times.
- LEETEUK!
- You had 10…
[Now it's a battle between the two]
Will it be LEETEUK or me?
- 13 times?
- 13 times, 13 times.
After being a prince for a day,
[The one who can't descend from his throne]
I must become a prince today.
That's what crossed my mind.
Ugh!!!
I wanted it so badly.
I was desperate for it.
[Versus the one who must rise to the top]
I'm really not gonna be a pauper.
If LEETEUK gets more than me,
[Will LEETEUK be the final prince today!?]
then LEETEUK will go on board.
[Or will it be SHINDONG?!]
If LEETEUK gets less than me,
I'll be the one going.
I will be
[A tense moment]
a prince, no matter what.
This is mine.
[Who will be the final prince!?]
[What will become of
their intertwined fate?!]
Ready!
- Challenge accepted!
- Let's go!
You can hear the woodpecker sound, right?
[1]
1!
[2]
2!
- Oh, nice
- Yeah, he's got it.
[A steady start]
Oh, I got a good feeling about this.
He's got it.
What's going on...
LEETEUK…
He's doing well.
I got a good feeling.
[6]
6!
[Quickly rising as a prince candidate]
[If he beats
SHINDONG's record of 13…!]
Oh?
[10]
10!
[11]
11!
[12]
12!
[Just 2 more to 1st place]
Oh!
Huh?
[12]
12!
[13]
13!
[LEETEUK hits it 14 times]
14!
I thought
my heart was going to explode.
Let's properly enjoy this.
Now…
My path is the highway!
Today, I am the prince!
Oh!
I unlocked it in one go!
Amazing! Wow!
Okay, it's just like yesterday.
You'll shout
"I'm the prince" and go on board.
I'm the prince!
[LEETEUK, DAWN, and JOHNNY
confirmed as the 2nd princes!]
(The pauper left behind)
JOHNNY…
- LEETEUK…
- Oh, JOHNNY!
[Do you remember this?]
Honestly, I’ve just given up.
[Back when we were sleeping on the ground...]
I don't know…
[When we were
just eating plain bread]
- LEETEUK…
- Oh, JOHNNY!
[We don't have to do that anymore…
We're princes now]
We finally moved up!
[Former pauper]
[And the current pauper, JISUNG]
Hey, hey, hey…
JISUNG's still here.
Oh, JISUNG...
[Belatedly noticed
their former youngest pauper]
Oh, sorry.
I got too happy.
I feel bad for JISUNG now.
Wow, I'm a double pauper…
A pauper-pauper.
[The world's first double pauper]
The first-ever pauper twice in a row.
I'm VIP.
(a.k.a. Paupert)
I'm a pauper expert.
I'm a Paupert.
[The princes' night]
[Night falls
on the tranquil cruise ship]
So, this is being a prince!
[Princes fit for a cruise arrive]
This is being a prince.
Oh, I'm so tired.
But...
We became princes
much faster than yesterday.
Right.
- Right.
- Yeah.
[After experiencing the pauper life,]
Oh, DAWN wouldn't understand.
[this moment is even more moving]
Going from pauper to prince.
You two must be so happy today.
Oh, this is so nice.
[Hurrying to enjoy the prince life]
This is what
being a king feels like.
Go in, go in.
[The 3 princes step aboard the cruise ship]
Wow!
- Oh.
- Oh, I smell something delicious.
[Let's unpack first]
We should unpack our bags first.
We saw the rooms earlier, right?
Oh!
There were 3 rooms.
And one was a suite.
[The cruise has 3 rooms]
[And only one is a suite room]
Oh, what?
I got the keys at the front.
[Who will get
the honor of the suite room?]
Come sit here.
(Finally sitting down N hours later)
Ohh!
[Not a magician]
I hold in my hands 3 cards.
You seem like a magician.
Rock-Paper-Scissors for the order.
[One of these is the suite room key!]
Let's play Rock-Paper-Scissors and take the card you want.
Is it the winner or the loser?
The winner?
- The winner.
- Okay.
Shoot or lose!
Rock-Paper-Scissors!
[JOHNNY is first]
JOHNNY, go first.
JOHNNY, you take one first.
You take one first.
Let's look at it at the end.
[JOHNNY makes his choice]
Okay.
Shoot or lose!
Rock-Paper-Scissors!
[LEETEUK is last]
Just take whatever.
[DAWN chooses his card]
Then I’ll take this one.
Okay.
[The honor of the suite room…]
- Let's reveal it.
- But how do we know?
Let's go!
[…will go to which prince?]
Oh, but…
Oh, whatever.
[Suite room]
Which one was the suite? Was it here?
I think it's this.
JOHNNY, you go first.
[JOHNNY will check his room first]
Or should the middle number go first?
I don't think it's me.
[Is JOHNNY's room the suite room?!]
Is it this one?
[Beep! Beep! Beep!]
Oh…!
[JOHNNY gets the premium room]
Even the sound is kinda annoying.
Alright, I'm going in.
[Is LEETEUK's room the suite room?!]
It sounds like, "It's definitely not you."
[Beep! Beep! Beep!]
[The honor of
the suite room goes to DAWN]
Hey, don't be too happy.
No, no, I'm…
You go in.
- Do I need to move to Egypt or something?
- But you know, if your card doesn't work,
then you can't go in either.
You'll be the only one
without a room.
[Suite room OPEN]
Oh!
But let's all take a look.
Yeah, yeah, let's take a look.
Let's go in.
This is driving me crazy!
- Oh!
- Wow!
[Speechless every time]
But honestly…
We could
all use this room together.
I know, right?
Wow, hey!
This is the same size
as our tent last night!
[A prince twice in a row
could never imagine the pauper life]
Seriously!
- Right here…
- The three of us, like this…
- Seriously.
- The three of us squeezed together…
Totally!
What? What is this?
Oh, my! Hey, hey!
[With the former paupers turned princes]
A bathtub?
[totally blown away]
Hey, what's this?
- The bathroom's so nice!
- Wow.
[The envious suite room tour ends]
Enjoy it while you can today.
- Yeah.
- You have to enjoy it.
[Let's meet again in our prince attire]
LEETEUK, if we change and come out, we can also…
Okay.
Wow, this is insane.
Do I have some
kind of connection with Egypt?
This is getting serious.
[Seriously considering moving here]
I don't have plans to move yet.
[Totally excited]
[The former paupers turned princes head to their rooms]
JOHNNY, get some rest. Rest up.
I'm gonna change and come out.
Get some rest.
Wow.
[Even loving the premium room]
Oh, this place is really nice.
Oh, wow!
[First, gotta unpack
his long-neglected suitcase]
[So excited…to open his suitcase for the first time]
Oh, I'm so excited, so excited.
I'm opening it
for the first time.
[As LEETEUK opens his tear-stained suitcase]
I feel like I'm gonna cry.
[JOHNNY also opens
his suitcase for the first time]
(Got his pajamas)
[After changing, he dives into the bed]
Oof.
[Ready to enjoy the prince life]
[What will their night be like?]
See you later, princes.
Let's enjoy it.
[The place the paupers will sleep]
We had it so good just yesterday.
[Meanwhile, the paupers head to the pauper accommodation]
I know, right?
Being here feels like déjà vu.
You were here yesterday.
[Same seats]
I was here yesterday, too
[Different destination]
This was DAWN's spot.
Oh, seriously, yesterday…
It was short,
but so good…
If only we had stayed
at yesterday's place longer…!
[The first princes' night was too short]
We didn't even get to try the pool.
Yeah, seriously, the pool!
Wow, but it was really nice there.
It was so cool to wake up
and see the pyramids there.
It would've been so amazing
if the weather had been better.
Like, it was
ridiculously right in front!
[Their prince days seem like a lifetime ago,
even though it was just last night]
If you step onto the terrace,
it's right there!
Team Pauper also had
something like a pyramid, too.
Dunes.
All around.
[Similar color]
Dunes everywhere. Yeah.
Yes, yes.
Agreed, agreed.
[Is this really Egypt?]
But honestly, it was really great.
Seriously…
I usually dream…
I usually have
a hard time sleeping.
But last night,
I slept like a baby.
So, I felt great today.
As expected.
I think it'll be fun.
I've been thinking.
[What if one person is a pauper all the way?]
If one person were a pauper all the way,
that'd be so fun, too.
And you're our only hope.
That one person…
[The one and only pauper-all-the-way candidate]
So, you're our only shot.
Oh, it's just me.
This is fun.
I don't think I'll ever forget it.
But, being born and raised in Korea,
there's something I find interesting.
"What would it be like
to live in a country with one season?"
I imagine it a lot.
That is pretty fascinating.
For Egyptians…
Snow is one thing,
but they just don't
experience winter at all.
- I know, right?
- Right.
I bet it only rains
once or twice a year in Egypt...
Maybe once or twice.
[Cairo sees about 15 rainy days a year]
They have to try a steamed bun.
[Luxor hardly sees any rain]
They have to try a pizza steamed bun.
[However]
Is it raining?
Is it actually raining?
- Oh, it's raining!
- It's raining!
[It's suddenly raining…??]
We're sleeping outside, hold on…!
[Emergency...]
This is an emergency.
Hey, we're in trouble.
[What are the odds of seeing rain in Luxor…?]
Of all days, it just had to be today.
On top of that,
we have to pitch the tent ourselves.
- Oh, really?
- Yeah.
While getting
soaked in the rain...
[Suddenly camping in the rain]
Wait, this is a bit…
They said it's a nice place.
Hold on a second!
[Feeling strangely uneasy...]
This is kind of weird.
Then, when we arrive,
will bread be waiting for us as our dinner?
[When it rains,
it pours for these paupers]
[After driving for a while,]
[an eerie scene unfolds]
Wait a second.
Are we…
What is this place?
Hold on, why this way…?
It feels like
a ghost will pop out…
What is this?
Did we take a wrong turn?
No way...
[With the tension rising]
Please, please, please.
[Where are the paupers headed?]
[The life of a prince]
LEETEUK!
JOHNNY, I just looked,
and the boat's moving.
I was looking outside.
The boat is moving, right?
Huh?
But I don't feel a thing...
Hold on.
Why?
I feel nothing at all.
No, I'm dizzy,
I'm feeling dizzy right now.
Really?
I'm really sensitive.
Wow, you're really sensitive.
Yeah.
[The princes' cruise sets sail]
We're moving, we're moving!
It's moving!
Wow, amazing!
[An exclusive service,
just for the princes]
[Enjoying Luxor on the water]
[And inside, the princes find ease]
Wow, there's even wifi too. This is awesome.
One Coke.
- One Coke?
- Yes.
[Instantly served]
Ice?
Yes, ice, ice!
Do you have beer?
One beer?
One beer, please.
- Oh, two beers!
[Ask and you shall receive
on the cruise]
- Thank you.
It's the first time
I've seen ice here.
[Precious ice]
It's my first time seeing ice.
This is really valuable right now.
That's right.
Princes!
Here's looking at you, kid!
Oh my God.
[This is the taste of success]
Wow!
It's great to sip something cold.
So nice.
I can't help but smile.
You feel so happy, huh?
I feel so happy.
Was it like this yesterday?
Oh, it was like this yesterday.
[This lighting]
But today,
[This temperature]
we can enjoy it even more.
Exactly.
[This humidity…Perfect]
- Princes! Princes!
- Princes!
[This is what being a prince is all about]
Wow, this place is nice.
My name is Princess.
Oops.
[Oh, you're a princess?]
Princess?
[Oops...]
Oh, sorry.
My name is Prince.
[Prince = Amir]
Prince Amir.
- Amir.
- Amir, yep.
Prince Amir.
(Prince 1)
Amir 1.
(Prince 2)
Amir 2.
[Former princess (Prince 3)]
Amir 3, yeah.
Thank you!
Peace be upon you!
Oh!
[Oh yeah!]
LEETEUK, you're amazing.
Oh!
What's for dinner?
[The blessing time never ends]
Steak, pasta.
M-m-mushroom soup.
Okay, I'll speak with the chef.
[There's a chef…???]
Oh, he said he'll tell the chef.
Wow!
This feels awkward for me.
It's awkward to
order something and have it come out.
[At your service]
It's usually not like this, but the chef is doing it!
[A customized dining experience just for the princes]
Hey, then let's just order everything.
Kimchi…Kimchi stew?
Pizza?
[Okay, order received]
Do you have Margherita?
Yeah, Margherita. Yeah.
[Even ordered steak, while they're at it]
We want medium.
- No, no.
- I want well done.
No, no.
Medium well done.
Medium.
Well done.
Medium well.
[They each have different steak preferences]
Yes, yes.
[Unlike their demanding taste buds,]
You know, you know, check, check.
Steak check.
[they're unable to hide their past pauper vibes]
Oh, why am I embarrassed?
My socks are a pauper's.
Hey, my socks...
- My socks are a pauper's.
- Me too.
[The hard-earned upgrade to royalty]
Hey, you're a pauper too.
[It's a night full of laughter]
I feel more grateful
for the little things.
Cold water...
Ice...
[The prince's newfound peace of mind]
The food that appears when you order.
I realized how
precious these things were.
[The laughter never ends in a prince's life]
I'm so happy I can't stop laughing!
[The pauper's life]
[Meanwhile...]
[Paupers arrive at an unknown location]
What, is it here?
Hold on, why this way…?
- It feels like a ghost will pop out…
- What is this?
(Where are we?)
Did we take a wrong turn?
Oh, we must have
taken a wrong turn, right?
[Suspicious, but getting out of the car]
Oh, what's this?
This is the place?
Wow, what's this?
Isn't this pretty decent?
Wait, are we
setting up a tent here?
Oh, the rooftop.
This is the rooftop?
[Today's pauper accommodation]
[The staff accommodation]
[The rooftop
of the staff accommodation]
[No elevators]
[The stairs will
take you to the rooftop]
Whoa, this is insane.
Hold on, this is so tiring!
Where are we? Is this it?
Huh?
- If it's this…!
- Wow, the breeze is nice
- What?!
- This is nice!
What's this?
- This is so pleasant.
- It's so nice.
- This is pretty decent.
- I'm happy with it.
- Oh!
- JISUNG, what do you think? Is this okay?
[Way better than expected!]
Crazy! It's crazy!
This is nice.
This is what
being a king is about!
Hey, hey, look at that!
Wow!
[The pauper accommodation they can't stop raving about?]
Wow, look at this view! Just wow!
This is seriously amazing!
This place has an amazing view!
Wow, I'm so impressed.
This place is insane.
[A smooth rooftop floor]
[A breathtaking view
of the ancient sites in the back]
[The Valley of the Kings]
[The pharaoh's secret tomb,
which was hidden deep inside a rocky mountain]
[to escape the endless
tomb raiding of the pyramids]
[Serving as a royal burial ground for pharaohs
from the 16th to the 11th century BC,]
[it provides a glimpse into the religion,
art, and funeral customs of the time]
[The final resting place
where pharaohs dreamed of eternity]
[And that very place
stretches out behind them]
This is amazing!
The view is fantastic.
The scenery is so beautiful.
Isn't this a painting?
- It's so gorgeous.
- I know, right?
Wow, the breeze is so refreshing.
The weather's just perfect right now.
[The 2nd generation paupers are satisfied]
Wow, this is more than enough.
I'm completely satisfied.
- We're basically princes at this point.
- We're really princes.
[Awesome]
This is something worth experiencing at least once.
[A minimal pauper kit]
They give us exactly 3 bottles of water.
And heat packs.
- Is that food?
- It's a humidifying mask.
[The paupert shares his knowledge with the rookie paupers]
I'm a pauper expert.
I'm a paupert.
This is our food?
Yeah, we did
have it for breakfast.
Oh, really?
But the floor here is pretty good.
- Isn't this pretty decent?
- It's amazing.
[Can immediately go to bed]
I could just fall asleep right here.
This is really nice.
[The paupert's body moves on instinct]
JISUNG knows how to do it. Do we just open it up?
You just have to open it up.
Right here.
- Like this, like this.
- That's right.
[Under the paupert's management, the tent setup begins]
Oh, okay, okay.
Oh, here's the strap.
We can hang it on this strap.
Oh, this is good.
It's more than enough.
- Not too bad!
- It's nice!
But if you go inside…
Did it get bigger…?
Oh, it's spacious!
[It feels like it got bigger overnight]
But why does it suddenly feel more spacious?
Hey, three people
can easily sleep here.
Was the tent always this big?
There's another one of these.
- Was it always this size?
- There's another one?
Was it always like this?
[Yes, it's the same tent]
I don't believe it.
JISUNG, just where
did you go last night?
I have no idea.
Just how did you guys
sleep last night?
Why'd you keep saying
it wasn't good when it's so nice?
You lied, huh???
Seriously!
Why would you say it like that?
Hey, this is so nice.
[Was it all a mirage yesterday?]
Was I too negative…?
No, but I'm sure…
(Squeezed in)
I slept so close to JOHNNY.
[Confused]
Wow, what is this?
JISUNG, this is so nice!
Oh, but…
[Still skeptical]
Is this really the same tent?
[Get it together and help with the sleeping bag]
Can you pull this out?
[No clue what's going on...]
[Today's aesthetic accommodation
that only JISUNG is confused by]
[So nice]
And then now…
- Hey, hey!
- Oh, what's this?
And then now…
- Hey, hey!
- Oh, what's this?
[With the paupert's lead, the club opens]
Hey, let's play some music!
Oh, this is nice!
[Just go with the beat]
- Oho!
- Ppa ppa-ppa ppa-ppa-ppa!
Egyptian Nights!
Arabian Nights!
It's Arabian Nights!
Oh, I'm dizzy.
[The paupers have a blast
with just a light]
Oh, tomorrow…
I feel kind of bad for the princes.
Let's pretend
we had it rough tomorrow.
[Planning to look as miserable as possible]
Yeah, we gotta act like we struggled.
For sure.
If they find out
we slept comfortably like this…
Totally.
LEETEUK will
start grumbling again. You know?
Ugh!!!
Was yesterday romantic?
Or is today romantic?
Today is romantic.
Did you know you can
see the stars? Look up!
You can see the stars.
I saw the stars earlier.
[The romantic paupers have the luxury to look up at the sky]
Once the lights are out, they'll be really visible.
Oh, hold on!
This is so nice!
[Not a single thing to complain about]
Wow!
- Wow, unbelievable.
- I think I can sleep here.
This is insane.
There was nothing different
from the pyramids that I saw at the hotel.
It was so breathtaking.
And there was a nice breeze.
Gasp!
I really loved it.
It just felt like a camping trip.
I could fall asleep right now.
I might just pass out.
[Sleepy]
[A spot too good to give up]
[And the princes who don't want to fall asleep]
- Steak.
- Wow!
They must really be
making it in the kitchen downstairs.
- Medium well done.
- Medium well.
Yes!
Oh, pizza, pizza!
[The glorious food comes one after the other]
Oh! Oh! Oh!
[Steak cooked to everyone's liking]
Wow!
This looks seriously delicious.
[The soup Prince Amir LEETEUK ordered]
Mushroom! Wow!
- Wow!
- LEETEUK, you really ordered well.
[A dining experience, exclusive to the princes]
Right? Right?
[The prince's elegant knife action]
How is it?
Is it tasty?
Mmm!
Mmm, delicious!
It tastes great!
Salmon and cream cheese.
Mmm!
[Salmon + avocado]
Oh, it's smoked.
[Maximizing the light and mild flavors]
It's delicious.
It's the taste of success.
I want to
sleep here again tomorrow.
Me too.
I know, right?
Honestly, I want to be
the prince a few more times.
[Why are you stating the obvious?]
I think everyone feels the same.
I wonder what we're doing tomorrow.
Since we did
individual matches today…
[The princes get ready for tomorrow]
It'll probably be 6 vs 6 tomorrow.
Oh!
I feel like
it'll be something like that.
I think it'll be
something huge tomorrow!
Because…
Today, we started late
because we had to travel.
Tomorrow,
we'll be here all day.
From what I can tell,
they're gonna use
whatever they can in this area
- and play games.
- Right, right.
I think it'll involve
the ancient sites.
Then tomorrow, we'll definitely
do horseback riding or an activity.
It'll definitely be
one of the two.
Yeah, I think
we'll definitely do it.
For sure,
it's one of those two, right?
[What kind of game will it be?]
[On the next episode]
A life-changing opportunity is waiting for you.
What could that be?
Whoa, what's this place?
[Taking place at the Luxor market]
The deeper we go, the cooler it gets.
Wow, I just saw
something amazing.
[The paupers' hidden mission]
A treasure hunt or something.
A treasure hunt?
This is hard, so hard.
How are we supposed to do this?
[The one dreaming of a status upgrade]
How do I do this?
I can't help!
[Why...]
I'm not happy.
[Overcome the hardships and challenges!]
I feel so blindsided.
Ugh!!!
[Who will seize
the chance for a status upgrade?]
[The next course is the ancient sites?]
Won't we do something while exploring the ancient sites?
[Bingo!]
Wow, wow!
[The Luxor Temple]
Now it really feels like I'm in Egypt!
I'm in Egypt!
Wow, seriously!
Wow, this is overwhelming.
It's truly mystical.
I'm kinda getting chills.
I'm getting goosebumps.
[And the status battle starts again]
Above the right eyebrow.
It's not.
Wow, I'm going crazy.
What could it be?
What's this, what's this?
[Oh…This… I know this…]
[I really want to be the prince]
Get it together!
Get it together! Get it together!
[No more pauper life!]
I've heard this! Oh, I'm going crazy!
Oh! Bread?
Hurry, hurry, hurry!
[An unpredictable battle to become a prince]
It's over, it's over!
I really want to do it.
This is driving me crazy!
[Who will become]
I am the prince!
[the 3rd princes?]